and pecking at their calves all the way.
All the men were gone except one.
Back in the yard, Boxer was pawing with his hoof at the stable lad who lay face
down in the mud trying to turn him over.
The boy did not stir.
>> He is dead.
I had no intention of doing that.
I forgot that I was wearing iron shoes.
Who will believe that I did not do this on purpose?
>> No sentimentality, comrade.
cried Snowball from whose wounds the blood was still dripping.
War is war. The only good human being is a dead one.
>> I have no wish to take life, not even human life.
>> repeated Boxer, and his eyes were full of tears.
>> Where is Mollie? exclaimed somebody.
>> Mollie, in fact, was missing.
For a moment there was great alarm. It was feared that the men might have
harmed her in some way or even carried her off with them.
In the end, however, she was found hiding in her stall with her head buried
among the hay in the manger.
She had taken to flight as soon as the gun went off.
And when the others came back from looking for her, it was to find that the
stable lad, who in fact was only stunned, had already recovered and made off.
The animals had now reassembled in the wildest excitement, each recounting his
own exploits in the battle at the top of his voice.
An impromptu celebration of the victory was held immediately.
The flag was run up and Beasts of England was sung a number of times.
Then the sheep who had been killed was given a solemn funeral,
a hawthorn bush being planted on her grave.
At the graveside, Snowball made a little speech, emphasizing the need for all
animals to be ready to die for Animal